getmein.com 2015-06-22

# GET ME IN! Buy & Sell Concert Tickets, Theatre Tickets and Sports Tickets.

**GET ME IN! Privacy Policy**

As a leader in our industry, GET ME IN! realises that earning and retaining your trust is of paramount importance and it's a responsibility we take very seriously.

This Privacy Policy sets forth our policies regarding the collection, use and protection of the personal information of those using GET ME IN!. Personal information (or “personal data” as defined in the Data Protection Act 1998) means any information that can identify a specific individual, such as name and, address, telephone number, e-mail address or credit card number.

We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy below. You should know that your personal information will never be shared with third parties except with your agreement.

This Privacy Policy explains the following:

What personal information does GET ME IN! gather from me and how is this information used?

When browsing our site, you are not required to provide any personal information unless and until you choose to make a purchase or sign up for one of our e-mail newsletters or other services as described below.

**Making a Purchase**

In order to purchase tickets and related services through our site, you must provide us with certain personal information such as your name, your credit card number and expiration date, your credit card billing address, your telephone number and your e-mail address. If you are buying tickets for one or more people other than yourself, you will need to make sure that each of these other travellers / clients agrees, in advance, that you may disclose their personal information to us.

**Client Registration**

In order to purchase tickets, you must provide us with your personal details for several reason including: (i) personal identification; (ii) to complete air, hotel, car, and other reservations; (iii) to allow us to contact you for customer service purposes, if necessary; (iv) to customise the content of our site to meet your specific needs; and (v) to make product improvements to our site. In addition, we need your e-mail address to confirm your booking of each ticket or other product you transact on our site. As a GET ME IN! client, you will also occasionally receive updates from us about ticket sales in your area, special offers, new company services, and other noteworthy items. However, you may choose at any time to no longer receive these types of e-mail messages.

**Client Profile**

As a GET ME IN! client, you can choose to complete your online profile by providing us with event preferences, credit-card billing information, delivery address, and other personal information. This information is primarily used to assist you in purchasing tickets quickly without having to type in the same information repeatedly.

**How We Use Personal Information**

Your personal information is used by us to contact you by post, phone or by email when necessary in connection with transactions entered into by you on the Site. From time to time, GET ME IN! may contact you by post or by email, with information or offers regarding upcoming events, products, services or customer surveys. If you do not wish to be contacted by GET ME IN! about upcoming events, products, services or surveys please contact us by emailing to [unsubscribe@getmein.com](mailto:unsubscribe@getmein.com).

GET ME IN! may from time to time, share your personal information with its affiliated companies, Ticketmaster UK Limited ("Ticketmaster") and TicketWeb UK Limited (“TicketWeb”). From time to time, Ticketmaster and/or TicketWeb may contact you by post or by email with information or offers regarding upcoming events, products, services or customer surveys.

If you do not wish to be contacted by Ticketmaster about upcoming events, products or services, please contact Ticketmaster by clicking the following link and inserting your email address into the link as indicated, https://www.ticketmaster.co.uk/member/unsubscribe?email_address=InsertEmailAddressHere , or send your request by post to TM Mailing Services, PO Box 43, London WC2H 7LD.

If you do not wish to be contacted by TicketWeb about upcoming events, products or services, please contact TicketWeb at [unsubscribe@ticketweb.co.uk](mailto:unsubscribe@ticketweb.co.uk) please type "Unsubscribe" in the subject line. Or send your request by post to TM Mailing Services, PO Box 43, London WC2H 7LD.

From time to time GET ME IN! may be authorised by the venue, promoter or organiser of an Event (“Event Partner”) to sell primary market tickets, including, without limitation, “platinum” seats. If you buy these tickets, you understand and agree that your personal information will be shared between GET ME IN! and the Event Partner for the particular event for which you are buying tickets in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our contractual relationship with the Event Partner. The Event Partner may contact you by post or by email, with information or offers regarding upcoming events, products, services or customer surveys. If you do not wish to be contacted by the Event Partner about upcoming events, products, services or surveys you will be able to unsubscribe from the Event partner’s mailing by following the unsubscribe link on the Event Promoter’s mailing or by contacting TM Mailing Services, PO Box 43, London WC2H 7LD.

**Promotions & Sweepstakes**

GET ME IN! frequently sponsors promotions and sweepstakes to give clients the opportunity to win tickets and related prizes. Information collected by us for such activities can include contact information and survey questions. We use contact information to notify contest winners and survey information to develop promotions and product improvements to the GET ME IN! website.

**Automatic Logging of Session Data**

We automatically log generic information about your computer's connection to the Internet, which we call "session data", that is anonymous and not linked to any personal information. Session data consists of things such as IP address, operating system and type of browser software being used and the activities conducted by the user while on our site. An IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet, such as our web servers, know where to send data back to the user, such as the pages of the site the user wishes to view. We collect session data because it helps us analyse such things as what items visitors are likely to click on most, the way visitors are clicking through the site, how many visitors are surfing to various pages on the site, how long visitors to the site are staying and how often they are visiting. It also helps us diagnose problems with our servers and lets us better administer our systems. Although such information does not identify any visitor personally, it is possible to determine from an IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider (ISP) and the approximate geographic location of his or her point of connectivity.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. There are many myths circulating about cookies, but you should know that cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable to do such things as run programs on your computer, plant viruses or harvest your personal information. The use of cookies is very common on the internet and GET ME IN!'s use of cookies is similar to that of such sites as Ebay, Yahoo!, BBC.com and other reputable online companies. First and foremost, you can rest assured that no personally identifiable information ("PII") about you (e.g., name, address, etc.) is gathered or stored in the cookies placed by the GET ME IN! web site and, as a result, none can be passed on to any third parties.

Our Site uses cookies to keep track of what you have purchased. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password (if you have supplied us with one) so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our Site, and for other purposes, such as informing you that you may have made multiple bookings for specific events on our Site. 

**Other**

From time to time we may add or enhance services available on the site. To the extent these services are provided and used by you, we will use the information you provide to facilitate the service requested. For example, if you email us with a question, we will use your email address, name, nature of the question, etc. to respond to your question. We may also store such information to assist us in making the site the better and easier to use.

**How can I opt-out of receiving your promotional emails?**

At any time, you can unsubscribe from our GET ME IN! newsletter or similar services through the provided link, accessible through the newsletter or by emailing [unsubscribe@getmein.com](mailto:unsubscribe@getmein.com).

You only receive e-mail updates from us about ticket sales in your area, special offers, new services, and other noteworthy items. We hope you will find these updates interesting and informative. Of course, if you would rather not receive them, please click on the "unsubscribe" link or follow the instructions in each e-mail message. GET ME IN! reserves the right to limit membership to those who will accept e-mails. Clients will be notified via e-mail prior to any actions taken.

**What safeguards are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of my personal information?**

All personal information you provide to GET ME IN! is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us.

**What other information should I know about my privacy?**

If you are a buyer, GET ME IN! will disclose your name, contact number and address details to sellers for order fulfillment purposes only.  
We use a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. We will disclose your name, billing address and credit card information to these credit card companies. But these companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes other than the billing for good and services. Additionally your contact details may be used by the courier as part of their address label to facilitate delivery and enable them to contact you directly in the event of any delivery issues. If you are a seller GET ME IN! may disclose your registered address _to a buyer_ for the return of _incorrectly delivered_ tickets. This will only happen if the event is within 3 days of the delivery of incorrect tickets. See section 3.6 of the Seller Agreement for further information. 

In addition to the circumstances described above, GET ME IN! may disclose client information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect the rights or properties of GET ME IN! or its affiliated companies or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. 

This policy is effective as of the publication date set out at the bottom of this page. Any material changes in the way GET ME IN! uses personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Statement. Of course, you may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Statement or our privacy practices via email. GET ME IN! will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries within five business days of receipt.

**Transfer of Your Personal Information and Financial Information Outside Of The EEA**

From time to time, GET ME IN may transfer your personal information and/or financial information to a company within the Ticketmaster group of companies or one of such company's agents or contractors in order to improve our services or to assist our security, credit risk or fraud protection activities. Such companies may be located outside of the European Economic Area, including in the United States, and you consent to the transfer of your personal information and financial information to such companies for the purposes set out in this paragraph. Whenever we transfer your personal information or financial information to countries outside of the European Economic Area, we will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted by the UK's Data Protection Act 1998 and related legislation from time to time.

**Transfer of Personal Information In Event Of Sale Of GET ME IN or Ticketmaster Or their Assets**

In the event that GET ME IN or Ticketmaster is sold, or some of their respective assets are transferred to another party, your personal information could be one of the transferred assets. If your personal information is transferred, use of your personal information will remain subject to this Privacy Policy. Your personal information will be passed on to a successor in interest in the event of a liquidation or administration of GET ME IN or Ticketmaster (as applicable).

This policy is effective as of November 11, 2008. Any material changes in the way GET ME IN! uses personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Statement. Of course, you may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Statement or our privacy practices via email, please contact us at legal@ticketmaster.co.uk.

 _Effective 19th June 2015_
